Guide to the Women's Refugee Commission Records, 1979-2020; 1979-ongoing, bulk 1989-2011 RL.01405
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Social Protection and Livelihoods Unit Series, 5 boxes
  - Columbia University School of International and Public Affairs project: Market assessment toolkit, 2008 (Box 30)
  - Fordham class, 2008 (Box 30)
  - Consultations with refugee women, regional and global, 2001 (5 folders) (Box 30)
  - Articles and references for the Refugee Survey Quarterly article on Refugee Women: 20 Years On (Box 30)
  - Reebok trafficking project donor reports, 2005-2006 (Box 30)
  - WRC work and sources on human trafficking and nexus with migration, 2005-2006 (3 folders) (Box 30)
  - Assessing the implementation of UNHCR's Age, Gender and Diversity Mainstreaming (AGDM) Initiative, 2000-2008 (5 folders) (Box 30)
  - AGDM pilot evaluation materials
    - Sierra Leone (Box 30)
    - Greece (Box 30)
    - Cairo (Box 30)
    - Zambia (Box 30)
    - India (Box 30)
  - Turkey AGDM assessment mission, 2005 (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - UNHCR AGDM Iniative evaluation, Ethiopia, 2009 (Box 30)
  - UNHCR AGDM materials and correspondence, 2005 (Box 30)
  - Making Cents conference presentation, 2009 (Box 30)
  - UNHCR Reference Group materials, 2008 (Box 30)
  - Teacher Compensation project, 2007 (Box 31)
  - Asibey Consulting project, 2009 (Box 31)
  - Board meetings, 2007-2009 (3 folders) (Box 31)
  - WRC Communications, 2008 (Box 31)
  - Women's Commission ethical guidelines, n.d. (2000s) (Box 31)
  - Population Council, MacArthur Project, 2008-2010 (Box 31)
  - Refugee Survey Quarterly article, 2010 (Box 31)
  - Accountability Working group, 2009-2010 (Box 31)
  - Safe School Initiative, 2007 (Box 31)
  - WRC work plans, 2007-2009 (Box 31)
  - Nike Foundation, 2006 (Box 31)
  - WRC meeting with Sir John Holmes, Undersecretary General for Humanitarian Affairs (UNOCHA) (Box 31)
  - UNHCR High Commissioner's Dialogue on urban displacement, 2009-2010 (Box 31)
  - Women At Risk work, 2006 (Box 31)
  - Washington DC trip, May 2006 (Box 31)
  - WRC Strategic Planning background documents, 2006 (4 folders) (Box 31)
  - Fordham class presentation, 2006 (Box 31)
  - AGDM NGO study, 2006 (Box 31)
  - Department of Peacekeeping Operations (DPKO) desk study, 2006 (Box 31)
  - World Food Programme (WFP) desk study, 2006 (Box 31)
  - Building Safer Organizations study-SG Bulletin and Model Procedures, 2006 (1 of 3 folders) (Box 31)
  - Building Safer Organizations, 2006 (Folders 2 and 3 of 3) (Box 32)
  - Starfish youth grant reports, 2007 (Box 32)
  - American Jewish World Service (AJWS) Education proposal, 2006 (Box 32)
  - Education and Livelihoods (South Sudan), 2006-2007 (Box 32)
  - Dadaab trip: Evaluation of Nike's Together for Girls Program, 2006 (Box 32)
  - Women's Commission delegation visit to San Diego, 2007 (Box 32)
  - Nepal trip and background documents, 2008 (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Board delegation background materials and correspondence, Thailand trip, 2006 (Box 32)
  - UNHCR miscellaneous meeting notes and correspondence, 2007-2009 (Box 32)
  - Livelihoods workshop logistics and agenda, 2009 (Box 32)
  - Presentation at Brookings Institute on urban displacement, Washington DC, March 2008 (Box 32)
  - Machel Plus 10 Strategic Review, 2003-2007 (Box 32)
  - Machel Review, Sierra Leone assessment, 2007 (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - UNFPA Tunisia meeting, 2007 (Box 32)
  - Youth Project, 2007-2008 (Box 32)
  - AGDM training, Washington DC, 2007 (Box 32)
  - UNHCR NGO Consultations, 2006-2007 (Box 32)
  - Refugee Girls' chapter and sources, 2006-2007 (Box 32)
  - Women's Commission-general/miscellanous documents, 2002-2005 (Box 32)
  - Boat People Initiative, 2008 (Box 32)
  - Fuel and Firewood project, 2006-2008 (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - UNICEF Child Protection project, 2008 (Box 32)
  - Advocacy blog, 2009 (Box 32)
  - Child Protection Section, 2007-2008 (Box 32)
  - Livelihoods Advisory Committee, 2006 and n.d. (Box 32)
  - Disabilities Project, 2007-2009 (Box 32)
  - Regional Livelihoods Workshops
    - Ghana, 2009 (Box 32)
    - Nairobi, 2009 (Box 32)
  - Gender-based Violence and Livelihoods report, 2009 (Box 32)
  - Bellagio Study: Improving Economic Practice and Policy Targeting Displaced Women and Youth, 2008 (Box 32)
  - WRC general, 2005-2006 (Box 33)
  - Masculinities, 2005 (Box 33)
  - Engaging Men and Boys to End Gender-Based Violence in Refugee Settings Workshop Held in Cape Town, 2008 September 22-25; 34 digital files extracted from an optical disc; approximately 27 megabytes (Digital-materials RL01405-SET-0007, Disk RL01405-OP-0012)
    Includes campaign materials and files for presentation, PDF, Word 97-2003, Powerpoint 2016 file formats.
  - Women At Risk, 2006 (Box 33)
  - Livelihoods Project, original proposals and briefs, 2006 (Box 33)
  - Thailand livelihoods workshop materials, 2009-2010 (Box 33)
  - Trafficking proposals, reports, and correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 33)
  - WRC Board delegation to Thailand, 2006 (Box 33)
  - WRC general, 2005-2006 (Box 34)
  - AGDM, 2004-2006 (3 folders) (Box 34)
  - Trafficking, 2006 (Box 34)
  - Protection and Participation, 2005 (Box 34)
  - Bellagio workshop, 2008 (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Colombia/Ecuador Trafficking Delegation, 2004 (Box 34)
  - UNICEF Adolescent Girls presentation, 2010 (Box 34)
  - Board delegation to Thailand, 2006 (Box 34)
  - Board delegation to Liberia, 2005 (Box 34)
  - Advocacy Day and Board meeting, 2008 (Box 34)
- Subject Files Series
  The Subject Files Series includes topical files primarily related to refugee women and their organizations; issues, such internal displacement, habitat, literacy, and resettlement; the Commission's participation and protection project; and education, especially in emergencies and for girls and adolescents. Other files are related to the Commission's partners in refugee work.
  Boxes 52-57 of this series are part of Accession 2016-0110.
  - International Rescue Committee, 1988, 1991 (Box 52)
  - Refugee Women
    - Articles, 1998-2002 and undated (Box 52)
    - Sudanese refugee women, 2000 (Box 52)
    - Nomination for WC Award, 1997-2000 (2 folders) (Box 52)
    - Dyfan, Isha, 1998-1999 (Box 52)
    - Fatana Ishaq Gialani, 1998-2000 (Box 52)
    - Duni Jones, 1997 (Box 52)
    - Fede, Betty, 1998 (Box 52)
    - Garcia, Maria Guadalupe, 1998 (Box 52)
    - Loung Ung, 1998, 2000 (Box 52)
    - Shqipe Malushi, 1993-2002 (Box 52)
    - Happy Mutesi, 1997 (Box 52)
    - Nsanzurwimo, Julie, 1998-2001 and undated (Box 52)
    - Veneranda D. Nzambazamariya, 1998-1999 (Box 52)
    - Maria Emma Prada, undated (Box 52)
    - Boríe, Rada, 1995-1996 (Box 52)
    - Mckonnen, Ayalnesh, 1999 (Box 52)
    - Bosnia, 1995-1998 and undated (Box 52)
    - Pilar Rueda, 2000 (Box 52)
    - Caritas Sebusharhu (Box 52)
    - Sima Wali, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
    - Refugee Experts, 1996 (Box 52)
    - Valenzuela, Carmen, 1998 (Box 52)
    - Mirecs, J. Williams, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
    - Jeredine Williams, 1997-2000 (Box 52)
    - Yezeshiwal Woldeamanuel, 1999 (Box 52)
    - Doris Mpoumou, 2003 (Box 52)
    - Sharma, Mangala, 1994-2002 (Box 52)
    - Orr National Conference, 1998 (Box 52)
    - Correspondence, Advocacy in Wa., 1989-1990 (Box 52)
    - York University, 1998 and undated (Box 52)
    - Protection articles, 2000 (Box 52)
    - Gender Mainster Assessment WC Planning meeting, 01/2001 (Box 52)
    - Advocacy Training, 1990-1995 and undated (Box 52)
    - African Training & Employment Srvc., 1994 (Box 52)
    - Jigyansu Tribal Research Centre, New Delhi, 1994 (Box 52)
    - CEPRODEP [Centro de Promocion y Desarrollo Poblacional], 1998 (Box 52)
  - Women's Comission Planning Meeting, 2001 (Box 52)
  - Refugee Women's Organizations
    - Bosnia Women's Initiative, 1997 and undated (Box 52)
    - BRAVVE [Bhutanese Refugees Aiding the Victims of Violence], 1998-1999 (Box 52)
    - Refugee Women in Development, Inc., 1999 (Box 52)
    - Refugee Women's Network, Inc., 1996-2003 (Box 52)
    - Mama Maquin, 1998 (Box 52)
    - Safia Siddiqu, 1999 (Box 52)
    - Rwandan Women's Association, 1994 (Box 52)
    - Self Help Initiative, 1997 (Box 52)
    - Migrant and Refugee Cultural Support, Inc., 1999-2000 and undated (Box 52)
    - Somalia, 1997 (Box 52)
    - Women of Srebenica Project, 1996 (Box 52)
    - Sudanese Women's Forum, Egypt, 1994 (Box 52)
  - Issues
    - Internally Displaced, Guiding Principles on IDPs, 1998-2001 (Box 52)
    - Internally Displaced, Publications, 1998-2001 (Box 52)
    - Humanitarian Aid, 1999 (Box 52)
    - Arms Sales, 2001-2002 (Box 52)
    - Conflict Resolution, 1994-1999 (Box 52)
    - Habitat, 1996-1999 (Box 52)
    - Human Rights, 1998-1999 (Box 53)
    - Income Generating, 1998 and undated (Box 53)
    - Literacy, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Micro Credit, 1997 and undated (Box 53)
    - Peace, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Landmines, 1993-2000 and undated (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - Psycho-Social, 1998-1999 (Box 53)
    - Mental Health, 1996 (Box 53)
    - Refugee Mental Health, 1997-2001 (Box 53)
    - Resettlement, 2000 (Box 53)
    - Trafficking, 1998-2000 and undated (Box 53)
    - Arms Trade, 1996-1997 (Box 53)
    - War Crimes, 1993-1996 and undated (Box 53)
    - War Crimes, Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 53)
    - War Crimes, Media, 1994-1997 (Box 53)
    - War Crimes, Tribunal, 1995-1999 and undated (Box 53)
    - NGO's 2002 (Box 53)
  - Marymount, Spring 1996, 1997 (Box 53)
  - Prep Comm, 1994 (Box 53)
  - Comments for Deirdre, 1994 (Box 53)
  - Deirdre, 1993 and undated (Box 53)
  - ISBN for Mellon Report, 1994 (Box 53)
  - Programs: Technical Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 53)
  - Survey Tool, undated (Box 53)
  - Conferences, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - Cairo Conference, 1994 (Box 53)
  - Deirdre's Travels, 1993-1994 (Box 53)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 53)
  - Background, 1989-1994 (Box 53)
  - UN Special Session for Children
    - Unicef NGO Steering Ctte Fundraising, 2001 (Box 53)
    - UN Prep Com: GA Spec Session on Children, 2000 (Box 53)
    - NGOs at Special Session (Unicef), 2000 and undated (Box 53)
    - Child Rights Caucus, 2000 (Box 53)
  - Winnipeg Conference, Sept 2000 (2 folders) (Box 53)
  - Field Assessment
    - Rwandan Women's Initiative, 1997 (Box 54)
    - Bosnian Women's Initiative, 1996 (Box 54)
  - UNHCR Guidelines, 1995-1997 and undated (Box 54)
  - UNHCR Correspondence on Guidelines, 1996 (Box 54)
  - Synopsis Questionnaire, 1996-1997 and undated (Box 54)
  - Urgent Action Gender Audit/ Baldons, Jan. 2000 (Box 54)
  - Gender Policies, 1996-1997 (Box 54)
  - Food Aid and Women, 1995-1997 (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Participation & Protection Project
    - NGO Working group, 1995-1998 (Box 54)
    - Public Presentations, 1995-1998 (Box 54)
    - Public Presentations, InterAction Forum, 1997 (Box 54)
    - Technical Advisor Workplan/Itinerary, 1994-1997 and undated (Box 54)
    - UNHCR Guidelines Evaluation/Synopsis, 1993-1997 (Box 54)
    - Food Management, 1996 (Box 54)
    - WFP [World Food Programme] Correspondence, 1995-1997 and undated (Box 54)
    - Project History, 1994-1995 and undated (Box 54)
    - Planning for 1998, Local Capacities, Project History (Box 54)
    - NGO group formation, Income Generating, Women in Livestock Development, 1998 (Box 54)
    - NGO group formation, NGO Meeting & Working Group, 1/1995 (Box 54)
    - NGO group formation, NGO Meeting, January 16, 1996 (Box 54)
    - NGO Group formation, UNHCR Guidelines Project Advisory Group, 1995 and undated (Box 54)
  - WFP: Gender & Participation in Emergency Food Aid, 1997 (Box 54)
  - UNHCR Guidelines Materials
    - Guidelines on the Protection of Refugee Women, 1995 and undated (Box 54)
    - Participation & Protection Project UNHCR Correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 54)
    - UNHCR Guidelines on the Protection of Refugee Women Correspondence, 1994-1995 and undated (Box 54)
  - B [Beijing?] + 10
    - BPFA [Beijing Platform for Action]: UNHCR, 1997 (Box 54)
    - BPFA: Women & Conflict, 1995 (Box 54)
    - MDG [Millennium Development Goals] Country Report, 2005 (Box 54)
    - BPFA, 2000 (Box 54)
  - Special Rapp. on Education, 2000-2005 (5 folders) (Box 54)
  - WP+S, Bethke, Lynne, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Technical Reports
    - Participation and Protection Project, OFDA (Office of Foreign Disaster Assistance) General Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 55)
    - Participation and Protection Project, 1997 West Africa (Box 55)
    - Participation and Protection Project, TA Reports: Internal, Rwanda, December 16, 1996 (Box 55)
    - Participation and Protection Project, 1997 Afghanistan/Pakistan Mission Contracts (Box 55)
    - Afghanistan Consultancy, 1996-1999 (Box 55)
    - Participation and Protection Project Technical Reporting, undated (Box 55)
    - Participation and Protection Project, IDP Guiding Principles, 1998 (Box 55)
  - IDP [Internally Displaced Person?] Guidelines
    - Issues, Internally Displaced Annotated Bibliography, 1998 (Box 55)
    - Internal Displacement report draft, 1999 (Box 55)
    - Local Capacities, UNICEF Proposal, April 1998, Gender and Displacement Project (Box 55)
  - Youth Statistics and Info.
    - Adol Research/Guide, 1998-2000 (Box 55)
    - Guiding Principles on wkg w/Adol (UNFPA), undated (Box 55)
    - Periodicals, 1997, 2002 (Box 55)
  - 2000 HCR Edu in Em. Conf (Box 55)
  - Edu in Em {Emergencies] 2001 WC/SSRC Conf (Box 55)
  - Educ in Emergencies Conf Nov. 1998 Norway (Box 55)
  - Refugee Education Trust Symposium, Sept. 2002 (Box 55)
  - Education in Emergencies, 1999-2000 (Box 55)
  - Teacher Training and Development, UN Youth Info Network, 1987-2000 (Box 55)
  - Teacher Training/dev, 1998-2000 (Box 55)
  - WC Edu in Em study/advoc., 1999-2000 (Box 55)
  - Edu in Em Case Studies/Programs
    - Refugee Edu Trust, 2000-2002 (Box 55)
    - UNESCO assessment of Edu in Em., 1999 (Box 55)
    - IRC Education, 2002 (Box 55)
    - Education in Em. Funding, 2001-2003 (Box 55)
    - Publications, 1995, 2000 (Box 55)
  - Adult Education, 1997-1998 (Box 55)
  - Peace Education, psychosocial well-being, 1996-2000 (Box 55)
  - Edu in Em articles, 1995-1998 (Box 55)
  - Edu in Em articles, 2001-2002 (2 folders) (Box 55)
  - UNESCO Youth NGO's, undated (Box 55)
  - CAC [Children in Armed Conflict?] info/stats, 1996-1999 (Box 55)
  - SSRC [Social Science Research Council] Jan 2001 Mtg. Virginia & NYC mtg (Box 55)
  - Adolescent & Girls Education
    - Adol/Youth Education, undated (Box 55)
    - Non-formal Educ (& AIDS) booklets, 2000-2001 (Box 55)
    - Reaching ch out of school, 1998 and undated (Box 55)
    - Doc project on Alb. adol from Kosovo, undated (Box 55)
  - Conv. on Rts of Child, Children's Rts Kits, 1995 and undated (Box 55)
  - Universities outreach letters--Raming, 2000 (Box 55)
  - International Assistance to Women Report, 2000 (Box 55)
  - UAF [Urgent Action Fund], undated (Box 55)
  - Zambia, 2000 (Box 55)
  - Turkey, 1999, 2004 (Box 55)
  - Sahel Women's Groups, undated (Box 55)
  - Azerb/Georgia, undated (Box 55)
  - P + P Women's Organizations (+IRC), 1999-2006 (3 folders) (Box 56)
  - Sphere Project Final, 1999 (3 folders) (Box 56)
  - Participation and Protection Project, Sphere Project, 1997 (Box 56)
  - Sphere Project, Chapter 1, 1998 (Box 56)
  - Sphere Project, Chapter 2, 1998 (Box 56)
  - Sphere Project, Chapter 3, 1998 (Box 56)
  - Sphere Project, Chapter 4, 1998 (Box 56)
  - Sphere Project, Chapter 5, 1998 (Box 56)
  - Adol/Youth Resources/ Biblio, 1999, 2001 (Box 56)
  - Rts training/Resources for kids, undated (Box 56)
  - Youth GPs in Africa, Asia, ME & LA
    - GYFA [Gulu Youth for Action] (Uganda), 2002 (Box 56)
    - Watwero Youth GP (Uganda), 2001 (Box 56)
    - Youth orgs in Sierra Leone, 2001-2002 and undated (Box 56)
    - African Movement of Working Children, 2001 (Box 56)
    - Kosovar Youth Council, 1999-2001 (Box 56)
  - SIDA ATHA Training, 2009 (Box 56)
  - UAMs [Unaccompanied ? Minors] Ethiopia, 2012 and undated (Box 56)
  - Bellagio, 2010 (Box 56)
  - UNFPA GBV Project, 2008-2009 (Box 56)
  - UNHCR Patricipatory Assessment Re-think, 2012 (Box 56)
  - Disabilities, 2011 (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Gates Foundation, 2006-2010 and undated (Box 56)
  - PRM [Bureau of Population, Refugees and Migration?], 2006-2008 (Box 56)
  - PRM GBV Year II, 2006-2009 (Box 56)
  - PRM Urban 2011 (Box 56)
  - PRM Migrating Risks, FY 2011 (Box 56)
  - NoVo [Foundation] Livelihoods, 2009 and undated (Box 56)
  - Kampala Background Docs, 2009-2010 and undated (Box 56)
  - Livelihoods Research-- New Delhi, 2009-2011 and undated (Box 56)
  - UNDP/BCPR Project, undated (Box 56)
  - LGBT, 2010-2011 and undated (Box 56)
  - Beyond Firewood, December 11-12, 2008 (Box 56)
  - Post-disaster impact on children, 2011 (Box 56)
  - Out of School Youth, undated (Box 57)
  - Masculinities, 2008 (Box 57)
  - Displaced Adolescent Girls Initative, 2012-2013 and undated (Box 57)
  - PRM Statelessness, 2013 and undated (Box 57)
  - New Delhi Assessment, 2011 (Box 57)
  - An Unsettled Future Conference, 7-8 December 2007 (Box 57)
  - Bellagio Livelihoods Workshop, 18-20 November 2008 (Box 57)
  - Fuel-Firewood, 2011-2012 and undated (Box 57)
  - NRC [Norwegian Refugee Council] Training, 2009 (Box 57)
  - ARC [American Refugee Committee International] Sub-grantee, 2006-2009 (Box 57)
  - IRC GBV, VSLA [Village Savings and Loans Associations] Burundi, 2007-2009 and undated (Box 57)
  - IRC Pilot Projects, 2006-2012 (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - DFID [Department for International Development], 2007-2009 (Box 57)
- Executive Director Files Series, 5 boxes
  Includes program materials and files for Executive Directors Mary Diaz, who served as director from 1994-2004, Carolyn Makinson, who served as director from 2004-2010, and Sarah Costa, who has served as director since 2010.
  Boxes 50-52 in this series are from Accession 2016-0110.
  - Mary Diaz
    - Catherine O'Neill, 1989-2002 (4 folders) (Box 50)
    - Ullmann, 1994-2000 (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - Board, Liv Ullmann, 1990-2001 (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - Archive, Mayotte, Judy, Comissioner, 1993-1995 (Box 50)
    - Arrangements, 2000 (Box 50)
    - Commissioners, Board Program and Policy, 2001 (Box 50)
    - Proposed slate for Board terms, 2003 (Box 50)
    - Women's Commission Board Meeting, June 6, 2000 (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - Women's Commission Board Meeting, New York, NY, September 16, 2000 (Box 50)
    - Board Meeting, February 25, 2000 (Box 50)
    - Strategic Planning Meeting, Staff, August 7, 2002 (Box 50)
    - Respect our rights partnership for equality dialog with refugee women, 2001 (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - UNICEF NGO Steering Committee letter, 2001; 1 digital file extracted from a 3.5-inch floppy disk; approximately 20 kilobytes (Digital-materials RL01405-SET-0001, Disk RL01405-FL3-0001)
      Includes fundraising letter regarding UNICEF NGO Steering Committee. Microsoft Word 97-2003 doc file format.
    - Intro Panel and Sponsor Orgs, 1999; 2 digital files extracted from a 3.5-inch floppy disk; approximately 60 kilobytes (Digital-materials RL01405-SET-0001, Disk RL01405-FL3-0004)
      Includes two desktop publishing files. qxd file format not supported.
  - Carolyn Makinson
    - International Council of Voluntary Agencies (ICVA), 2002-2009 (6 folders) (Box 34)
    - Advocacy, 2004-2008 (Box 34)
    - Detention and Asylum, 2004-2006 (Box 34)
    - Humanitarian Accountability Partnership (HAP), 2005-2010 (Box 34)
    - Reproductive Health, 2005-2007 (includes 1 CD with flash movie) (Box 35)
    - Fuel and Firewood, 2006-2010 (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Education, 2005-2008 (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Protection, 2006 (Box 35)
    - UN Security Council Resolution 1325, 2006 (Box 35)
    - UN Security Coucil Resolution 1820, 2008 (Box 35)
    - UNHCR, 2006 (Box 35)
    - Egypt delegation, 2004 (Box 35)
    - Care and Protection of Children in Emergencies, n.d. (Box 36)
    - Livelihoods, n.d. (Box 36)
    - Watchlist for Children and Armed Conflict, 2005-2010 (Box 36)
    - Internal Displacement, 2004-2007 (Box 36)
    - Women's Commission transcripts, 2004 (Box 50)
    - Strategic Planning, 2006 (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Meeting file, Carolyn, October 2004 (Box 50)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Meeting file, Carolyn Makinson, March 2005 (Box 50)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Advocacy Day file, Carolyn, 2005 (Box 50)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Meeting file, Carolyn Makinson, 12 May 2005 (Box 50)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Meeting file, Carolyn Makinson, October 2006 (Box 50)
    - Board delegation to Liberia, 2-12 December 2005 (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - Board delegation to Thailand, 22 June -3 July 2006 (Box 51)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Meeting file, 11 May 2006 (Box 51)
    - Women's Refugee Commission Luncheon, May 6, 2010 (Box 51)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Meeting file, October 23, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Women's Refugee Commission Luncheon, May 7, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Meeting file, October 10, 2008 (Box 51)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Meeting file,10 May 2007 (Box 51)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Meeting file, October 12, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Meeting file, 20 March 2007 (Box 51)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Meeting file, 9 March 2006 (Box 51)
    - Women's Commission Board of Directors Meeting file, October 14-15, 2005 (Box 51)
    - Peterson, Holly, 2010 (Box 51)
    - Dina Habib Powell, 2007-2008 (Box 51)
    - Sandee Pyne, 2006 (Box 51)
    - Ranaan, Susan, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Mary Robinson, 2008 (Box 51)
    - Fran Rodgers, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Roff, Nathalie Ho, 2007-2009 (Box 51)
    - Lynn Rothschild, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Vicki Sant, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Lynn Savarese, 2006 (Box 51)
    - Schneider, Pauline, 2008 (Box 51)
    - Judith Shapiro, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Shmavonian, Nadya, 2009-2010 (Box 51)
    - Mangala, Sharma, 2001-2008 (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - Stephanie Sluka, 2006-2007, undated (Box 51)
    - Subbiah, Ponni, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Susman, Sally, 2008-2009 (Box 51)
    - Than, Tharaphi, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Sheryl WuDunn, 2008-2009 (Box 51)
    - Weissman, Harriet, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Wertheimer, Sarah, Board, 2008 (Box 51)
    - Zischke, Cree, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Catherine O'Neill, 1997-2011 and undated (Box 51)
    - Kazickas, Jurate, 1994-2009 (Box 51)
    - Judy Mayotte, 1994-2008 (Box 51)
    - Beverlee Bruce, 1994-2009 and undated (Box 51)
    - Newland, Kathleen, 1997-2007 and undated (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - Peruggi, Regina, 1998-2008 and uindated (Box 51)
    - Barbara Crossette nomination, 2006 (Box 51)
    - Hefner, Christie, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Bellamy, Carol, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Bertini, Catherine Ann, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Bodine, Barbara, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Browde, Beth, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Cashin, Stephen, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Cooper, Helene, 2008 (Box 51)
    - Ranny Cooper, 2006-2007 (Box 51)
    - Copeland-Carson, Jacqueline, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Cymbalista, D.C., 2009 (Box 51)
    - Davis, Lanny J., 2008 (Box 51)
    - Frances, Deng, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Dimandja, Agnes Loteta, 2008 (Box 51)
    - Disney, Abigail, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Fitt, Lawton, 2008-2010 (Box 51)
    - Sonia Pressman Fuentes, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Jain Guest, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Hooda, Sheila, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Hoodfar, Homa, 2008 (Box 51)
    - Iskenderian, Mary Ellen, 2008 (Box 51)
    - Khera, Farhana, 2008 (Box 51)
    - Lamont, Annie, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Matthews, Cynthia (Whitehead), 2007 (Box 51)
    - Alejandra Matus, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Mayai, Augustino "August", 2009 (Box 51)
    - McKinley, Janet, 2008 (Box 51)
    - Pat McPherson, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Jane Molner, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Nastasi, Lisa, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Parham, Kasia, 2009-2010 (Box 51)